ukbride.co.uk 2014-04-05

# UKbride Privacy Policy

## Data Protection

UKbride has been created by Whitespace Publishers Ltd. The site is populated under its Editor and Data Controller, Julian Wilkinson, of Whitespace Publishers Ltd.

You have certain rights under the Data Protection Act 1998 including a right to request a copy of the information we hold about you (for which we will charge an administration fee of £5.00). You also have the right to ask us to correct any inaccuracies in your personal information (which is free), or to unsubscribe to receiving information from UKbride. To make such a request, send an email to [datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk](mailto:datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk). including the email address that you registered with along with your full postal address and postcode.

This privacy policy may change without notice, therefore, it may be useful to check back periodically to note any changes.

For information on the Data Protection Act 1998, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and the Information Commissioner please go to [www.dataprotection.gov.uk](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/)

## Personal Information

The site stores personal information of those creating an Eternity membership login name and password. Information pertaining to this will be kept on our servers along with details you submit both relating to your wedding planning and to those who you have entered into our My Guest List, My Table Plan and My Address Book. Brides may send you an email if you choose to publish your email address via the site.

Where you provide personal information, we will use this information to/deliver the services you have requested, and for our internal administration and marketing purposes. We share your personal information with selected third parties to enable us to tailor specific marketing towards you, in the form of emails, brochures, and to a very select quantity of suppliers, your telephone number. If you do not want us to do this please accept the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy and **UNCHECK THE BOX** which says "Please ensure I receive FREE information from UKbride's parners; suppliers of products and services which I may find useful during my wedding planning." If you subsequently feel you no longer wish to have your details passed on please email [datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk](mailto:datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk) including the email address that you registered with along with your full postal address and postcode and we will no longer pass on any of your details. You will also need to let these companies know that you would rather not hear from them again, which you can do by simply using the unsubscribe link in any of their emails, or contacting them using the details that will be included in every communication that they send you.

In addition, the site automatically logs the user's IP address and session information such as the duration of the visit and the type of browser used. This is recognised by the Web server and is only used for system administration and to provide statistics, which Whitespace Publishers Ltd may compile to evaluate site use.

Whitespace Publishers Ltd may contact you from time to time via email, post or telephone to offer products or services pertaining to the UKbride site or our high quality magazines. Should you not wish to receive such communications, please inform us by contacting our data controller by emailing [datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk](mailto:datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk). 

## Financial Details

Whitespace Publishers Ltd do not store any Credit/Debit card or bank details of any kind on the web site. Credit/Debit card details are also not held on any other electronic or paper based system.

## Disclaimer

Please note that the links to other businesses on our site and information found on the site is neither an endorsement nor a recommendation of those products, services or businesses, but are for information purposes only. Information received from third party companies is neither a recommedation nor an endorsement by Whitespace Publishers Ltd. Whitespace Publishers Ltd cannot accept any liability in relation to products or services found on the site.

## Intellectual Property

Any material found on this site, including text or images, may not be printed, copied, reproduced, republished, downloaded, posted, displayed, modified, reused, broadcast or transmitted in any way, except for your own personal non-commercial use. Permission for any other use must be obtained from Whitespace Publishers Ltd by emailing us at [datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk.](mailto:datacontroller@whitespacepublishers.co.uk.)

The names, images and logos identifying UKbride, are proprietary marks of UKbride. Copying of material except for personal or non-commercial use is not permitted without prior approval from the relevant copyright owner. Requests for such permission should be directed to Whitespace Publishers Ltd, tell us who you are, the organisation you represent (if any) and how and why you wish to use our logo. Please include your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address.

## Virus Protection

We make every effort to check and test material at all stages of production. It is always wise for you to run an anti-virus program on all material downloaded from the Internet. We cannot accept any responsibility for any loss, disruption or damage to your data or your computer system which may occur whilst using material derived from this website.

## Hyperlinking to UKbride

You do not have to ask permission to link directly to pages hosted on this site. We do not object to you linking directly to the information that is hosted on our site. However, we do not permit our pages to be loaded into frames on your site.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. UKbride may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer's hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser's help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by UKbride to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimise load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by UKbride to store, for example, whether or not you want your password remembered, or other such information. Cookies used on the UKbride Website do not contain personally identifiable information.

UKbride

Elm Grange Studios

East Heckington

Lincolnshire

PE20 3QF

**Tel** : 01529 469977 | **Fax** : 01529 469978

**V.A.T. Number** \- 797 0927 74

Last updated 18th April 2013
